Viewers all over the world,
we want to be like Jesus.
We want to be like Jesus in our heart.
We pray for right focus, in the name of Jesus.
Whatever is disturbing you right now, our heart is always going up and down
you think about this and think about that - leave it for God.
We pray for right focus, in the name of Jesus!
Right focus, in the name of Jesus.
Begin to receive a hearing heart.
A hearing heart.
Viewers all over the world,
I separate you from familiar spirits.
Viewers all over the world, begin to confess every loophole,
every area the familiar spirits are using to attack you.
It is using your weakness to attack you.
It is using your weakness to get to you.
Begin to confess those weaknesses. Begin to confess them...
Every area familiar spirits, satanic spirits are using to get to you, to attack you -
confess them right now before we sack them.
It is time to sack them!
It is time to give them a quit notice; it is the hour to give them a quit notice.
In the name of Jesus, begin to confess those weaknesses.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, have the quit notice and begin to serve it to satan,
serve demons the quit notice.
Here is the quit notice!
This is notice!
Right now, out of my life; out of my temple.
Give them a quit notice right now; serve it to them!
Quit! This is a quit notice I'm serving you right now!
I'm giving you a quit notice to leave my life, business, finances
to leave my career, family, marriage, country!
to leave my life. This is quit notice, this is notice!
Out!
Viewers all over the world,
yes, I know the challenges you have; God knows better.
Whatever challenges in your health, be it your bones, kidneys, liver, blood
are you unable to walk or are you on sickbed?
Whatever challenges, sickness is sickness.
Never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Be cured, in the name of Jesus!
Dry bones shall rise again.
Whatever and wherever the sickness, disease is in your body,
ignorantly you may not know,
I say, be removed in the name of Jesus!
When Jesus says, "Be removed", who can say no?
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
The name all names bow to -
all knees shall bow, all tongues shall confess.
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
At the name of Jesus, at the command of Jesus, I remove that sickness!
It is well
It is well with your soul, blood, kidney, muscles, liver!
It is well!
Rejoice!
RV: Mel Flowers 27/03/2019